Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- D(ba) Finland, Series XXVII
  - D(ba)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings. General Methods
    - D(ba)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - D(ba)530 Bible Study
        - D(ba)530.4 Meetings, announcements
          - SCM Bible study prospectuses, 1911 (Box 104, Folder 859)
      - D(ba)531 Bible classes and circles
        - D(ba)531.2 Leadership
          - Ohjeita, 1912 (Box 104, Folder 859)
      - D(ba)532 Text-books
        - Items listed in card catalogue, 1902-1923 (Box 104, Folder 859, 860)
      - D(ba)534 Cycles of study
        - Various cycles, 1904-1906 (Box 105, Folder 861)
    - D(ba)540 Mission study and service
      - General
        - Tehkaa Jeesus Kuninkaaksi!, 1912 (Box 105, Folder 861)
      - D(ba)544 Mission service. Obligations as to missions implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
        - Mita Vastaamme (Box 105, Folder 861)
      - D(ba)547 Education, secular and religious, of natives in mission lands
        - D(ba)547.2 Medical
          - Albert Schweitzer, AArniometsan Laakarina, 1922 (Box 105, Folder 861)
      - D(ba)549 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
        - D(ba)549.1 Reports
          - AFMF, 1903 (Box 105, Folder 861)
    - D(ba)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
      - D(ba)555 Institutions and Organizations for Social Effort by Students
        - D(ba)555.1 For People in Congested Cities
          - Personaallinen Palvelus (Box 105, Folder 862)
      - D(ba)556 Social morality
        - D(ba)556.1 Economic, political, and moral conditions of women
          - Nuoren Miehen Suhde Neitoon, 1915 (Box 105, Folder 862)
          - Den Kristna Kvinnan Och Sedlighetsfragen, 1902 (Box 105, Folder 862)
  - D(ba)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Special Classes of Students
    - D(ba)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - D(ba)610.3 Service cards and blanks
        - Invitation blank cards (Box 105, Folder 863)
  - D(ba)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - D(ba)702 University catalogs. Educational bulletins
      - Keisarillinen Suomen Aleksanderin --Yliopisto, 1899 (Box 105, Folder 863)
  - D(ba)800 Correspondence
    - D(ba)801 John Mott with
      - Ole Andersin, 1908-1911 (Box 105, Folder 864)
      - Eelis Gulin, 1925-1939 (Box 105, Folder 864)
    - D(ba)810 Ruth Rouse w/
      - Elena Eklund, 1903-1905 (Box 105, Folder 865)
      - Louise af Forselles, 1903-1913 (Box 105, Folder 865)
      - Helmi Forsman (Mrs. Eelis Gulin), 1911-1923 (Box 105, Folder 866)
      - Ruth von Pfaler, 1912-1914 (Box 105, Folder 867)
  - D(ba)900 History
    - General
      - Odd documents on Finland, 1903-1904 (Box 105, Folder 867)
      - Documents re. Finnish SCM including accounts of Nadendal Scandinavian Student Meeting (1921), 1920-1924 (Box 105, Folder 867)
      - Kristillisen Nuorisolikkeen Voittoja Nykyaikana, 1914 (Box 105, Folder 868)
    - D(ba)911 Report of progress. Year books
      - Pyhilta Tulita, 1926 (Box 105, Folder 868)
    - D(ba)920 Biography in general
      - Martti Luther, 1918 (Box 105, Folder 869)
      - Paul Nicolay (Finnish and Swedish), 1921 (Box 105, Folder 869)
    - D(ba)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and Legislative
      - General
        - D(ba)960.16 Official reports: Nuorten Parissa Undessa Maailmassa, 1914 (Box 105, Folder 870)
      - D(ba)961 Plenary conferences
        - Kutsumus and Inbjudan, 1902-1914 (Box 105, Folder 870)
        - Wiipuri, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 871)
        - Jakdostad, 1905 (Box 106, Folder 871)
        - Pietarsaaressa, 1905 (Box 106, Folder 871)
        - Savonlinnassa, 1906 (Box 106, Folder 871)
        - Nyslott (Box 106, Folder 871)
      - D(ba)966 Secretaries' Schools
        - Calls to prayer (Box 106, Folder 871)
      - D(ba)968 Leaders' Conferences
        - Abo, Turku, Finland -- program, 1926 (Box 106, Folder 871)
      - D(ba)969 Student Discussion Conferences
        - Jyvaskylassa, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Turku, 1901 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Wiborg, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Jakobstad, Pietarsaaressa, 1905 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Nyslott, 1906 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Kesak, 1907 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Iaskokus, Ekenas, 1908 (Box 106, Folder 872)
        - Kuopiossa, Kuopio, 1909 (Box 106, Folder 872)
- D(bb) Norway, Series XXVIII
  - D(bb)000 General
    - D(bb)011 Publisher's prospectuses, trade lists, announcements
      - God og Billig (Box 106, Folder 873)
  - D(bb)100 Objects and Field, Extension and Supervision
    - General
      - Norges Kristelige Studenterbeuegelse (Box 106, Folder 873)
      - Til Norske Studenter Af Alle Fakulteter (Box 106, Folder 873)
    - D(bb)120 Relationships and polity
      - D(bb)123 International
        - Den Kristelige Bevaegelse ved Universiteterne I Amerika, Europa Og Asien (Box 106, Folder 873)
  - D(bb)200 Buildings and Rooms
    - Norske studenters Kristelige forbund (Box 106, Folder ????)
  - D(bb)300 Organization, Incorporation
    - D(bb)310 Constitution and Membership
      - Copies of statutes and regulations, 1899-1918 (Box 106, Folder 873)
    - D(bb)330 Membership
      - D(bb)332 Basis
        - Flyer re. (Box 106, Folder ????)
  - D(bb)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings. General Methods
    - D(bb)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - D(bb)512 Personal work texts
        - Fyldt Af Aanden, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Ideal Straeben Og Religios Tro, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Livets Kunst, 1907 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Til Studerende, 1912 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Fremtidens Religion, 1911 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Nutidshristendom, 1907 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Taler fra motet paa Eidsvold, 1909 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Studenter Trahtater, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Fra Sommeren, 1917 (Box 106, Folder 874)
        - Gjennembruddet, 1904 (Box 106, Folder 874)
      - D(bb)514 Work for Schoolboys and Schoolgirls
        - D(bb)514.1 Camps
          - Gymnasiaster Paa, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 875)
          - Jordbruksarbeide, 1918-1919 (Box 106, Folder 875)
    - D(bb)520 Devotional and inspirational. The Morning Watch
      - General
        - Morgenvagten, bon Enrum, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 875)
      - D(bb)522 Days and weeks of prayer
        - D(bb)522.1 Calls to prayer
          - Meddelelse, 1898 (Box 106, Folder 875)
          - Indbydelse til almindelig Bonnedag for stendenter, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 875)
        - D(bb)522.2 Prayer cycles, Litanies, and daily helps
          - Weekly cycles, 1905 (Box 106, Folder 875)
        - D(bb)522.3 Song books, religious poetry
          - Hymn: Allheims Drott (Box 106, Folder 875)
    - D(bb)530 Bible Study
      - D(bb)532 Text-books
        - Jesu Liv og Gjerning, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 875)
    - D(bb)540 Mission study and service. SCM. YWCA. Foreign departments
      - General
        - D(bb)540.1 Bibliography
          - Studenternes Missionsforenings bibliothek, 1889 (Box 106, Folder 876)
        - D(bb)540.2 Statistics and atlases, charts
          - Statistisk oversigt over hedningemissiones stilling, 1889 (Box 106, Folder 876)
      - D(bb)544 Mission service. Obligations as to Missions implied in Xnty and resting upon the Church
        - D(bb)544.4 Need of support at home in men, money, and prayer, and works toward these ends. Student missionary campaigns
          - Universitetspraediken, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 876)
          - Jesus Som Konge, 1898 (Box 106, Folder 876)
      - D(bb)545 Enlistment for life work in missions
        - Sekretaermission, n.d. (Box 106, Folder ????)
      - D(bb)549 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
        - D(bb)549.1 Reports
          - Aarsberetning for Studenternes Missionsforening, 1894 (Box 106, Folder 876)
    - D(bb)550 Social Study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions.
      - D(bb)552 Text-books
        - Samfundets Kristianisering, 1914 (Box 106, Folder 876)
      - D(bb)555A Institutions and Organizations for Social Effort on behalf of students
        - Til Alle Norsek Studenter! European Student Relief, n.d. (Box 106, Folder ????)
  - D(bb)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Special Classes of Students
    - D(bb)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state associations
      - D(bb)615.8: Haandbok for Studenter ved Kristiana Universitet, 1891-1920 (Box 106, Folder 877)
  - D(bb)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - D(bb)702 University catalogs. Educational bulletins
      - Det Kongelige Frederiks Universitet, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 878)
    - D(bb)710 Other organizations of students or other classes having interests similar to those of the Federation
      - Kristiana. Laerernes vennekreds (Box 106, Folder ????)
    - D(bb)750 Organized lines of work and study
      - D(bb) 751 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
        - D(bb)751.2
          - Opad!, 1918 (Box 106, Folder 879)
          - Bli Med!, 1919 (Box 106, Folder 879)
          - Fremad Marsj!, 1917 (Box 106, Folder 879)
        - D(bb)751.22
          - Under Forvand-lingens Lov, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 879)
          - Livs-Retningen, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 879)
          - Hoad or det at tro?, 1899 (Box 106, Folder 879)
      - D(bb)752 Devotional and inspirational
        - D(bb)752.22
          - Andagts-bok, 1918-1919 (Box 107, Folder 880)
          - Trost Fra Gud, 1917 (Box 107, Folder 880)
      - D(bb)753 Bible study
        - D(bb)753.1
          - Var Bibeltimer, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 880)
        - D(bb)753.09
          - Det Norske Bibelsels-kab, 1905,1905, 1915 (Box 107, Folder 880)
      - D(bb)754 Mission study and service
        - D(bb)754.44
          - Til Arbeide For Schret-aermissionen!, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 881)
    - D(bb)790 History
      - D(bb)795
        - Den Unges Ven, 1899 (Box 107, Folder 881)
  - D(bb)800 Correspondence
    - D(bb)801 John R. Mott with
      - K. Martin Eckhoff, 1897-1914 (Box 107, Folder 882)
      - Prof. Michelet, 1909-1924 (Box 107, Folder 883)
    - D(bb)810 Ruth Rouse with
      - Olga Bredel, 1904-1906 (Box 107, Folder 884)
      - Margarete Folkestad, 1911-1912 (Box 107, Folder 884)
      - Norwegian Women Students leaders, 1910-1917 (Box 107, Folder 884)
      - Ingeborg Rynning, 1916-1920 (Box 107, Folder 885)
      - Katherine Seip, 1904-1907 (Box 107, Folder 885)
      - Haldis Ziener, 1915-1923 (Box 107, Folder 886)
  - D(bb)900 History
    - General
      - Historical documents re. SCM, 1915-1924 (Box 107, Folder 887)
      - Fred Talle Farer, 1922 (Box 107, Folder 887)
      - Kristelig Studenterberaegelse, 1900 (Box 107, Folder 887)
      - Til Norske Studenter Af Alle Fakulteter, 1906 (Box 107, Folder 887)
    - D(bb)910 Reports
      - Aarsoversigt for 1901, 1902 (Box 107, Folder 888)
      - D(bb)911.1 Directories: NSKF (Box 107, Folder 888)
    - D(bb)950 Periodicals
      - Gymnasiast Bladet, 1925 (Box 107, Folder 888)
      - Deiliger Jorden, 1913-1916 (Box 107, Folder 889)
    - D(bb)960 Conventions and conferences, educational and legislative
      - D(bb)961 Plenary conferences
        - Indbydelse, 1904 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Helgelandsmoen, 1906 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Framnes, 1907 (Box 108, Folder ????)
        - Notodden, 1908 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Eidsvold, 1909 (Box 108, Folder ????)
        - Holmestrand, 1913 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Framnes, Hardanger, 1915 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Gran, Hadeland, 1915 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Bakketun I Vaerdalen, 1916 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Haakenstad-Roa, 1919 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Lillehammer-Klepp, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Lillehammer, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 890)
        - Trondenes, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 890)
      - D(bb)968 Leaders' Conferences
        - Lillehammer, 1912 (Box 108, Folder 891)
        - Holmestrand (Box 108, Folder 891)
      - D(bb)969 Student Discussion Conferences
        - Lillehammer, 1912 (Box 108, Folder 891)
- D(bc) Sweden, Series XXIX
  - D(bc)000 General
    - D(bc)011 Publisher's prospectuses, trade lists, announcements
      - One catalog and one leaflet, 1919 (Box 108, Folder 892)
    - D(bc)030 Service cards and blanks including questionnaires, record and subscription blanks and membership cards
      - various blanks (Box 108, Folder 892)
    - D(bc)070 Works by officers and members not directly related to the SCM
      - Rudberg, G. "Ur Platons Brevvaxling", 1921 (Box 108, Folder 892)
      - Silen, E. "Speglarna Vid Downing Street", 1922 (Box 108, Folder 892)
  - D(bc)100 Objects and Field, Extension and Supervision
    - General
      - Sveriges Kristiliga Studentroelse, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 893)
    - D(bc)120 Relationships and polity
      - D(bc)123 International
        - Kristliga Studentvarlds forbundet (1899). (Box 108, Folder 893)
        - John R. Mott, (1914 -- Karl Fries), 893 (Box 108, Folder 893)
      - D(bc)127 To special classes of students
        - D(bc)127.1 Theological
          - Handwritten statements; relations between Free Church students and SCM, 1913 (Box 108, Folder 893)
  - D(bc)300 Organization, Incorporation
    - D(bc)310 Constitution and Membership
      - SCM (Box 108, Folder 893)
  - D(bc)500 Organized Lines of Work and Study. Religious Departments and Meetings.
    - D(bc)510 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
      - General
        - Bjorkquist, M. "Religionsundervisningen i folkhogsholar", 1913 (Box 108, Folder 894)
        - Mott, J. "Ardlig vackelse vid ett universitet", 1909 (Box 108, Folder 894)
        - Rodhe, E. "Kristerdomen och Sholan", 1918 (Box 108, Folder 894)
      - D(bc)512 Personal work texts
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 109, Folder 895)
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 110, Folder 895a)
      - D(bc)513 Life work in religious callings
        - Ekland, "Prastens Kall" (Box 110, Folder 896)
      - D(bc)518 The individual as citizen. The war. Church and state. Church History
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 111, Folder 897)
    - D(bc)520 Devotional and inspirational. The Morning Watch
      - General
        - Liedgren, E. "Den Svenska Psalmboken", 1910-1914 (Box 112, Folder 898)
        - Mott, J. "Morgenvakten Bon i enrum" (1912), "Jesus Khristus En Verklighet" (1916), "Forbon Det Viletigaste Just Nu" (1914), "Bibelstudium" (1916) (Box 112, Folder 898)
        - Rudin, W. "nagralardomar om bonen", 1918 (Box 112, Folder 898)
      - D(bc)521 Prayer meetings
        - Eklund, J. "Var Hogmassogudstjanst" (Box 112, Folder 899)
      - D(bc)522 Days and weeks of prayer
        - D(bc)522.2 Prayer cycles, Litanies, and daily helps
          - Luther, M. "Var Kristra Tro", Gudsfruktan och Gudsfortrostan (Box 112, Folder 899)
          - Mannstrom, O. "Vid Helgsmal", 1922 (Box 112, Folder 899)
        - D(bc)522.3 Song books
          - Two hymns (Box 112, Folder 898)
    - D(bc)530 Bible Study
      - General
        - Brun, L. "Huru Skall Jag Lasa I Bibeln", 1917 (Box 112, Folder 900)
        - Genterwall, O. "Hur Skola Vi Lasa VarBibel?", 1912 (Box 112, Folder 900)
      - D(bc)532 Text-books
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 112, Folder 901)
    - D(bc)540 Mission study and service. SVM. YWCA Foreign Departments
      - General
        - Om missiorsroelsen bland Amerikas studenter i vara dagar (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - Den Evangelisken Missionen, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - Hvad har den Kristna varldsmissionen utrattat?, 1918 (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - Foreningen Krinnliga Missions Arbetare, 1916,1920 (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - Svenska Kyrkans Mission, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - Missionsuppgifter och Missionsproblem, 1921 (Box 113, Folder 902)
        - D(bc)540.2 Statistics and atlases, charts: Maps of Africa and other countries drawn up by Karl Fries -- late 1800's (Box 113, Folder 903)
        - D(bc)540.4 General meetings, announcements, programs: Notices for Upsala, 1895,1898 (Box 113, Folder 904)
      - D(bc)541 Mission study. Methods and organization
        - Skolan Och Missionsstudiet, 1917 (Box 113, Folder 904)
      - D(bc)542 Text-books
        - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 113, Folder 904)
      - D(bc)544 Mission service. Obligations as to missions implied in Christianity and resting upon the Church
        - General
          - Folke/Fries. Var fids missionsproblem. Konferensen: Konstantinopel, 1911 (Box 113, Folder 905)
          - Mott. Mannens uppgift i Varldsmissinen, 1913 (Box 113, Folder 905)
        - D(bc)544.1 Motives of missions
          - Johnson. Hvad skola vi svara hednamissionens motstandare?, 1912 (Box 113, Folder 905)
        - D(bc)544.2 Need for missions
          - Lindberg. Varldsmissionens Lage Efter Krigsaren, 1920 (Box 113, Folder 905)
        - D(bc)544.3 Claims of Christianity over other religions. Comparative religion. Apologetics
          - Andre. Kristendomen Den Fullkomliga Religionen?, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 906)
          - Aulen. Evangeliskt Och Romerskt, 1922 (Box 113, Folder 906)
          - Fogelklon. Protestant och Katolik, 1919 (Box 113, Folder 906)
          - Lehmann. Kristendomens Stallning Inom Religionerna, 1915 (Box 113, Folder 906)
          - Wikander/Jonsson. Kristus och Indien, 1909 (Box 113, Folder 906)
      - D(bc)547 Education, secular and religious, of natives in mission lands
        - Sandegren. Indiens Studenter och Kristendomen (Box 113, Folder 907)
      - D(bc)549 History of the student missionary movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
        - General
          - Konungens Arende Hastar!, 1914 (Box 113, Folder 907)
        - D(bc)549.2 Biography of missionaries
          - D(bc)547.23 Of native Christians
            - Stokes. Arjun, 1911 (Box 113, Folder 907)
        - D(bc)549.5 Periodicals
          - Svensk Missionstidskrift, 1911 (Box 113, Folder 907)
    - D(bc)550 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
      - D(bc)552 Text-books
        - Rowan. En Harforare I Kampen Mot Noden, 1916 (Box 113, Folder 908)
      - D(bc)554 Social service. Obligations as to community service implied in Christianity and resting upon the church
        - D(bc)554.1 Enlistment of voluntary service
          - Lutteman. Arbetarevarldens Religiosa Problem, 1911 (Box 113, Folder 908)
      - D(bc)556 Social morality
        - D(bc)556.1 Economic, political, and moral conditions of women
          - Ribbing. Om Kvinnohyllning I Forntid och Nutid, 1917 (Box 113, Folder 908)
  - D(bc)600 Associations in Individual Institutions or among Social Classes of Students
    - D(bc)610 Colleges, universities and student departments of metropolitan and state universities
      - D(bc)611 Objects and field, extension and supervision
        - Article re. Lordagsforeningen, 1898 (Box 113, Folder 909)
      - D(bc)613 Organization, Incorporation
        - D(bc)613.1 Constitutions
          - Various SCM constitutions, 1886-1910 (Box 113, Folder 909)
      - D(bc)615 Organized Lines of Work and Study
        - D(bc)615.1 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
          - D(bc)615.12 Personal work texts
            - Items here are listed in card catalog (Box 113, Folder 909)
        - D(bc)615.2 Devotional and inspirational
          - Mott. Bibelns studium, 1899 (Box 114, Folder 910)
          - Povlsen. Bonnen, 1904 (Box 114, Folder 910)
          - D(bc)615.223 Song books: Missionsanger, 1887 (Box 114, Folder 910)
        - D(bc)615.3 Bible Study
          - D(bc)615.32 Text-books
            - Jeremia, 1907 (Box 114, Folder 910)
        - D(bc)615.4 Mission study and service
          - General
            - Fries. Missionstaken Bland Varldens Studenter, 1897 (Box 114, Folder 911)
            - Speer. Varldens Evangelisering I Denna Generation, 1904 (Box 114, Folder 911)
            - Wilder. Bland Indiens Studenter, 1899 (Box 114, Folder 911)
            - Lagerheim-Bjorck. Den Norska Madagaskar-missionen, 1905 (Box 114, Folder 911)
            - Nutida Missionsuppgifter, 1906 (Box 114, Folder 911)
            - D(bc)615.401 Bibliography: Missions bibliographies, 1884,1907 (Box 114, Folder 912)
            - D(bc)615.402 Statistics Skematisk ofversikt af de svenska missionerna, 1890 (Box 114, Folder 912)
            - D(bc)615.403 Blanks: Membership blank (Box 114, Folder 912)
          - D(bc)615.44 Mission service. Obligations
            - D(bc)615.444 Needs of support:Holmberg. Prasten sasom arbefare for Hednamissionem, 1897 (Box 114, Folder 912)
          - D(bc)615.45 Enlistment for life work in missions
            - Warneck. Hednamissionen, 1897 (Box 114, Folder 912)
          - D(bc)615.49 History of the student Missionary Movement as distinguished from the SCM as a whole
            - Bilder ur Missionshistorien, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 913)
            - Kristi Intag I Drottningens Af Saba Land, 1906 (Box 114, Folder 913)
            - De Svenska Missionerna, 1904 (Box 114, Folder 913)
            - D(bc)615.491 Reports:Student Missionary Association of Upsala, 1884-1888 (Box 114, Folder 913)
            - D(bc)615.4912 Executive:, 1897-1898 (Box 114, Folder 913)
        - D(bc)615.5 Social study and service. Community welfare work, religious and philanthropic, outside of student body. Home missions
          - Sociala Fragor, 6 vols., n.d. (Box 114, Folder 914)
          - Sociala Sporsmal, 6 vols., 1907-1908 (Box 114, Folder 915)
          - Ord Till Korsfararne, 1909 (Box 114, Folder 916)
      - D(bc)619 History, 1901-1911
        - Uppsala Kristliga Studentforbund (UKS), 1901-1911 (Box 114, Folder 916)
        - D(bc)619.1 Reports:UKS, 1905-1907 (Box 114, Folder 916)
    - D(bc)660 Associations among special classes
      - D(bc)662 Women Students
        - D(bc)662.31 Constitution:Svenska Kvinnors Missionsforening, 1903 (Box 114, Folder 916)
  - D(bc)700 Student Life in General Outside the Federation
    - D(bc)702 University catalogs. Education bulletins
      - Upsala, 1895,1898,1899 (Box 114, Folder 917)
      - Medical College, Stockholm, 1899 (Box 114, Folder 917)
      - Lunds Konglig Universitets, 1898 (Box 114, Folder 917)
      - Studerande Nationers I Upsala Historia (1595-1877) (Box 114, Folder 918)
    - D(bc)720 Other organizations of students or other classes having interests similar to those of the Federation
      - Article re. Kristliga foreningen, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 919)
    - D(bc)750 Organized lines of work and study
      - D(bd)751 Evangelistic and philanthropic work among students
        - D(bc)751.2
          - Rudin. Sadeskorn, 1892 (Box 115, Folder 919)
          - Wallinder. Den Kristna (Box 115, Folder 919)
          - Ridderlighetens Regel, 1908 (Box 115, Folder 919)
        - D(bc)751.8
          - Lundin. Aterblick pa det 19:e arhundradets religiosa rorelser, 1900 (Box 115, Folder 919)
        - D(bc)755.6
          - Rudin. Nykterhetstal, 1900 (Box 115, Folder 919)
          - Ett bref fran Pontus Wikner, 1899 (Box 115, Folder 919)
    - D(bc)790 History
      - D(bc)791 Reports
        - Kristtiga foreningen af Unge Man i Stockholm, 1899-1914 (Box 115, Folder 920)
      - D(bc)792 Biography
        - En Banbrytare (Box 115, Folder 920)
  - D(bc)800 Correspondence
    - D(bc)810 Ruth Rouse with